Okay, should be transcribing that one.
Just want to make sure.
Okay. Yeah, it's transcribing.
So I am going to give you a
semi-structured interview on your study
habits because I want to understand how
you're currently studying with regard to
like your modules, quizzes, exams, etc.
Like whatever you feel best fits,
you can make the answer for.
So it's like if you don't study at all
for quizzes, let's just say
We're not going to focus on places.
If it's like mostly exams,
we're going to be looking mostly at exams.
Yeah. I'm here to interview.
It's going to take roughly 20 minutes.
You're fine to overrun,
but I have this room for another 27,
26 minutes.
So we can only overrun a little bit.
So I'm going to be doing some
requirements gathering.
So the more data you give me,
like the longer your answers,
the better for me.
But don't just ramble for the sake of
rambling.
All right,
so I'm going to be taking a few notes
just so I can make callbacks and have
greater context about you.
I'm gonna get started. OK,
so what module did you do this semester?
Ayaa.
I did Mechatronics Insurance Society
designed to.
That's not fair.
Um...
We take analysis, and yeah,
it was analysis and sensitive.
I've interviewed you from your, go for it.
Data and now.
Okay, which one was the most difficult?
And this is subjective, like, uh,
I'm gonna go with Nextronics. OK, yeah,
seems to be a common factor.
Um, yeah,
do you want to rank the rest of them? Uh,
I found design, well,
the difficulty is more on like motivation
to do it. Yeah, that's,
I think that's entirely fine. Yeah.
Like that is a reason to find difficult.
Uh, design probably the lowest. The #5?
Yeah. Okay. Um.
Sense systems.
Three. Okay.
I don't know, they call it two and four,
yeah.
Uh, 4 is probably data from us. OK,
I'm an engineer in society, yeah.
That's interesting. OK, so.
You said mechatronics was hardest.
Was it because of your aforementioned
motivation or was it actually just
difficult?
The content inside it was pretty
straightforward.
It's just doing circuits in a lab,
but the...
success rate of those surfaces is very
low.
So we'd have faulty equipment or not too
helpful TAs because of the faulty
equipment.
So it's just running around the circles.
So what kind of equipment would be faulty?
So we'd be given Arduino kits. Oh, right,
yeah.
Those would be faulty from previous
groups who've done it incorrectly.
So it was fixed. Okay.
Have you tried a different module? Yeah.
And 13 more times of that. Okay,
that makes sense.
So it's like a hardware failure.
Would you say that the course itself
wasn't too difficult?
The course itself content-wise wasn't.
Okay,
so the maths and physics inside of it is
completely fine. Okay, so difficulty.
Edwards.
Yeah,
and so a lot of side projects that I do
with. Yeah,
that's probably why I know all this stuff.
OK,
what about the rest of the engineering
society? Why was that difficult?
The group projects that they put out for
aren't enjoyable to me because it relies
a lot on the entirety of the group
putting in that part.
Yes, okay. So it's like the team working.
Yeah. Yeah.
And sensors, again, team project sensors.
Yeah, it was another group project,
but the group project was easy.
It was just rushed. It still wasn't.
The time frame for it was terrible,
so it was just.
And then data analysis.
Data analysis was pretty easy.
It is a shell. Yeah,
they extended that point because why it's
not an engineering design also. OK,
excellent.
Do you study for these modules a lot on
your free time? I study for design.
And I did study for mechatronics before I
realised that the content was easy.
I thought it'd be similar to electronics,
but not. Fair enough, yeah.
Do you use Moodle a lot for that,
or do you use like other types of tools?
So I cheque Moodle and look at the specs
in terms of like...
If they've given out a lecture schedule,
then I look at the topics on the lectures
and research those first for the week. So,
when you say research those,
do you just use Google, do you use AI,
do you use like YouTube videos?
I use Google,
and then based on the results for
in-depth topics, like research,
just census, and then...
Find the topic in there, such in YouTube,
and I find a video on YouTube. So, OK,
yeah, so YouTube just wanted to be aware.
Third party tools.
Would you say that Moodle is useful for
finding out your topics? Yeah.
What about the content on Moodle,
like the lectures and tutorials?
Are those useful?
It depends on the lecture.
So some of them will upload the full list
of lectures.
Some of them won't and only release it
week by week. Yeah.
Which one do you prefer?
I prefer it all at once because they need
to plan it a lot easier and you can just
look at the topics
So that was hard or I've never heard of
this one. Yeah,
I like to read ahead to you. Yeah, OK.
Do you structure your day for studying
like?
I don't structure it necessarily by half
like days or I'm studying this day for X
amount of time.
How do you decide to do that?
Uh, it's usually in the study break,
so yeah,
like for the times where we aren't
scheduled for university. Oh right, okay.
So it's like between classes or do you
mean like reading week? Uh, it'll be,
so my timetable this term has had like
one day free on Wednesday, for example.
So Wednesday is usually just the
I'll look at things I have seen, yes,
and then in the reading it could be just
study day three other day. Alright,
fair enough. That's a good strategy.
Managed mobile back.
Do you prioritise the modules in a
certain way?
Arhin.
I'm prioritising by motivation.
So if I enjoy a module,
then I tend to work on a little more.
That makes sense, yeah.
So it's all about how much you enjoy the
module. It's directly correlated.
How much effort you put in? Yes. Right,
that makes sense.
Do you use different strategies per
modules? Like if you're low motivation,
will you study in a different way?
The strategies depend on whether it's a
coursework module or an exam module.
So most of these modules are coursework
modules this term,
but last term was quite a lot of exam
modules. Right.
So how do how do how does your study
strategy differ?
So for the coursework modules, it's.
a lot of not hands on,
like actually doing projects related to
it,
whereas the exam ones are looking at past
papers. So for electronics, for example,
it does have a past paper to look at or
data analysis,
they put up a past paper to look at.
So I'll be going through that and
checking topics.
Do you feel like you're learning less?
by doing pause papers compared to like
coursework.
My understanding is a lot less doing
exams, but a bit of course work,
'cause I don't exams are very.
This is the answer to this question.
What's cool is a why is this the answer
to this question? Like go explore. Yeah,
that makes sense.
Do you have your study materials easily
accessible when you study?
Like for instance on Moodle, sure,
but do you download them to like your
local drive?
Do you have them structured in a nice
file structure or?
Usually it's just me was to grab the
lectures and then how do they just look
at the lectures?
Have them your downloads or?
Do you actually put them into like
folders?
It'll just be, I don't. Alright, OK.
By the end of the term,
when it's like having to crunch down,
then all of the lectures will have been
uploaded,
and if we're having a MIT semester quiz,
then they don't tend to bring in content
from the future. No, that's true. OK,
fair enough. Do you,
so you don't really arrange the study
materials to just download them as you go?
OK.
How do you feel about Moodle offerings
when they're studying the structure?
You've already complained about like some
professors only uploading week by week
versus uploading all at once.
What about like the nuance in how they
upload?
Sometimes they won't upload the tutorial
answers until like a week later. Oh,
that's.
I'm not a fan of that because it requires
you to go to those tutorials and
sometimes you're not need to be able to
go to those tutorials. Yeah, why?
So if you stuck on a question like you
just don't have the answer until. Yeah,
but then why can't you be at the
tutorials? Like events. OK, sure. Yeah,
that's like tough, I guess. OK, do you?
So you've already mentioned you use
YouTube sometimes to help you study.
Do you?
Use anything like notebook LM like notion.
Like this kind of stuff,
I don't tend to use notebooks. Well,
I used to just write something like paper
book. OK, now I use a smart tablet,
so I just write it down. OK,
so is it like an iPad and use like the
notes application or OK?
Sun.
Do you feel like any of these other like
AI tools help you?
I haven't delved into them a lot.
I feel like they could help with daily
structuring,
like if I had a routine for studying,
maybe, but I don't tend to.
It's just I would do it on this day.
Whenever you call a deadline coming up.
Yeah. Understandable. Yeah.
That makes sense.
I want to talk a little bit about your
study environment now.
So,
where do you normally study in my bedroom?
I have lots of monitors like different
material,
and I find it difficult to a lot of what?
Sorry, monitors, monitors, right? Yeah,
I find it difficult to have material just
on one device where I'm not going to be
able to just flip my eyes to it, right?
So you'd like to have, for instance...
The questions and the answers open at the
same time. Not really. The questions.
I'll be doing the questions and I'll
cheque the answers after like just
staring at the answers. But for example,
if I have content that I'm trying to
apply and I need the content open with
the questions at the same time. OK.
Yeah, it's still existing one questions.
Yeah, I mean,
that's one of the reasons I don't like
studying on a laptop.
So what makes a good study space?
Is it the monitor real estate?
Are there other things that...
A quiet place usually helps quiet, yeah.
Yeah,
the big thing is being able to have
multiple resources over, I think,
at the same time. Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, I would do the same.
So, do you live with your family?
Do they distract you when you study,
or do you say, "I'm studying,
please don't distract me"?
They tend to not distract me.
It's most of my family is either at
school or at work,
so on the days that I don't have
university,
I just sit at the phone and study in my
room without distractions. Yeah,
that makes sense.
I would like to ask,
so if your family's at home,
do they bring you snacks when you're
studying? For instance, like some crisps?
No? No food in your room? Well, I mean,
I bring food up in my room.
Do you like to study?
Do you like to eat while you study or?
It depends on the motivation of the food
is there, so the whole MOOSA. Right,
that makes sense. OK, fair enough.
Do you study in any other places other
than your room,
or is it like that's where you got the
majority of your work done?
I do a lot of coursework at University of
Woolsworth Council. Yes, it does. Why?
Why didn't you do that at uni?
Because my room is associated with
studying, having a bunch of stuff open,
it's easy to just put other material up
and have that on the side while I'm doing
coursework,
which usually is more interesting than
the course itself.
So removing myself from that in
university.
That's really good information actually,
so thank you for that one.
So, and in your room,
you probably have troubles with sometimes
distracting yourself when you need to do
coursework. Yes. Okay, correct.
Bye.
OK,
so I want to now talk about your actual
study sessions themselves.
When you do your studies,
do you do it alone with others or it's
just a variety?
It becomes more with others as the
deadline gets closer usually since most
of my friends start also studying at the
same time.
But usually, alone,
I try and get the base understanding of
something on my own. OK,
and then in those subsequent panic
sessions, it's cool.
I try and explain the topics to others,
which I felt,
which I think helps my understanding.
It absolutely does,
because you need to explain it in many
different ways sometimes.
How do you coordinate that?
Do you just do like a Discord thing at
everyone and studying and doing? Yeah,
pretty much. OK, fair enough.
How do you track what you did in the
session?
Up.
For me, I have my tablet, iPad,
and so I have different folders for each
subjects and within the folder I have
exam bits where although this is for this
exam or topic folders within that where I
have notes and topics.
Usually when a specific exam is coming up,
I just make a folder and
and then.
Will you like cheque things off when
you're done or? Not really.
So I go through a session,
you do like a paper. Sure, yeah.
And then I'll have the notes I've made
from that like up on the slide,
so I can explore some PDF. I don't know.
Different monitor,
so I refers my notes there, and then...
The next session,
I'll look at what I did last time as like
a refresher and then. Well,
that's that's how I know. Yeah,
that makes sense. OK, I'm gonna walk.
I'm gonna ask you to walk me through like
a typical sort of study session.
Do you have your laptop here with you?
Yeah.
You've got about 10 minutes for this, so.
Okay.
It'll be fine, don't worry about it. Yeah,
I see other calls.
Right, still haven't figured out. Ideally,
we'd be able to join this team's call and
share your screen,
so I could get a recording or...
I understand it can be difficult on the
Nyx sometimes to share a screen. Yeah.
But this is the last big task of this
interview zone.
Yeah.
So, the team, like, yeah, I got it.
Awesome. Do you want me to tell you? OK,
so I'm gonna move a little bit.
I can see your screen.
I want to make sure that it is also
sharing because I will be watching this
part back at least once or twice. Yeah.
Yeah, perfect. OK, awesome.
See, I can look next science,
so I can see it here.
Don't need to like look over your
shoulder. Yeah, so, well, for example,
I've got that 10th April deadline.
Alright, yeah.
Of
So walk me through how you prepare for
this. Well,
the peer review isn't really that,
but we'll do. The data analysis one? Yeah,
data analysis, of course.
So this was originally for Tuesday.
But they've extended it. So first,
I'd look at the course description and
try and glean and think this gas turbines.
Yeah. So in the explanation,
they mentioned it was an AI task.
And so that would just be gathering.
Uh, data from processing it, um.
Conveniently,
they outlined the tasks there, so...
Follow tasks, I guess,
so you just follow the task one by one,
right? OK, that makes sense. So,
do you have like the task up on one
monitor and the stuff to do the task on
another, or yeah, so, like,
on do it on me? Yeah, no, I understand.
I have them, like,
side by side on the boxes.
I think they want us to do this in our
Jupiter notebook. Yeah, but...
Yeah, yes.
Okay.
Of course, I was just kind of doing it.
Um, if I go to a different module,
it's like an exam module, I think. Yeah,
electronics is passed,
but I can never look at it. Sure,
that's totally fine.
They had all their tutorials listed,
so usually I just go through the
tutorials and do the tutorials and then
attempt the mock paper,
so they've added a mock paper here. Yeah.
And I don't know if they added solutions
at the end,
but I'd have this up on one screen.
Or would you say that the solutions
always have like worked examples? Uh,
it depends on the lecture.
I find it helpful when they are worked
examples. Why?
It gives you a thought process to follow
and not understand, but like a model.
This is.
the way you should think of this module.
Yeah, that makes sense.
If there is no worked example,
do you plug it into like an AI to see
like the worked working?
Do you do this often or do you do this
only when you really can't figure out?
Usually only when I can't figure it out.
They tend to follow the tutorials for the
most part, so.
If I usually try and find a tutorial
that's as close to the questions as
possible and follow the works,
works reasoning for that.
That makes sense.
So what about past papers?
If you open those,
do they have like worked examples for all
of the questions or? Depends on.
They usually do.
Um...
But on the ones where you don't
understand,
then that's either for the group call for
people to understand, or...
Got a tutorial, right? OK.
I wanted to also, I guess,
completely flipped my mind.
This is something.
Right, okay, I guess I just dropped it.
Okay, do you use any other sites? Oh yeah,
YouTube videos.
Would you watch like a YouTube video that
might show how to solve that kind of
problem?
It's not usually about solving promise.
The YouTube video is usually for
understanding the topic, right?
So you do that for the start of the
semester, yes,
or like whenever you get to a topic that
you struggle with. OK,
can you get that core understanding from
the YouTube video? OK, that makes sense.
So it's not like a oh ****,
it's the exam time I need to revise,
but it's more of like a I'm building my
understanding, yes.
Okay, cool. Yeah, that makes sense.
How do you gauge session success,
like study session success?
It's usually based on whether I can do
the test that I'm trying to understand.
So it's going to be lecture topic.
If I don't understand talking in the
lecture, then YouTube video,
and then attempt the tutorial.
If I don't,
then I guess that's not successful, right?
OK, so yeah.
That makes sense. Cool. Okay.
Thanks for your time and participation.
Before we wrap this up,
is there anything else that you'd like to
add that I may not have covered?
No, really, no. OK, deal. Alright,
I'm gonna stop the recording here.